Guide to the Edmund White Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 1997 Acquisition, 1982-1996; Series XIV; 10.21; (11 boxes)
  - Computer media, (2 computer disks)
    - MAC format. System 7.5.1 Microsoft Word 5 May '96, 1997-ycal-0122-r-0001; 1 (Box 54)
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - [no label information], 1997-ycal-0122-r-0002; 1 (Box 54)
- October 1998 Acquisition, 1974-1997; Series XV; 7; (7 boxes)
  Purchased from Pierre Beres on the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 1998.
  Contains magazines, clippings and printed ephemera by or relating to Edmund White.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 23.
  Box 61 (audiocassettes and videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Kalstone letters, 1974, undated (Box 55)
  - Correspondence, 1994; 2 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence, 1997; 9 (Box 55)
  - "AIDS to Understanding", undated; 2 (Box 56)
  - "MISS PICKET FENCE: Elton John Starts a New Life", undated (Box 56)
  - Notebooks, undated; 3 (Box 56)
  - "Record Time", undated (Box 56)
  - "Violets for Her Furs", undated (Box 56)
  - "Terry Gross: The Voice of Listening America", undated (Box 56)
  - "A Sled on the Steppes", undated (Box 56)
  - Stonewall and After: Sexuality and Politics in the Work of Edmund White, MA dissertation by Les Brookes, 1996 August (Box 56)
  - Original Youth: The Real Story of Edmund White's Boyhood by Keith Fleming, undated (Box 56)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 56)
  - "Life with my Uncle Edmund White", by Keith Fleming, undated (Box 56)
  - See Under: LOVE by David Grossman, printed, 1988 (Box 56)
  - "He's One, Too", by Allan Gurganus, printout, 1996 (Box 56)
  - The Truth About Lorin Jones by Alison Lurie, printed, 1988 (Box 56)
  - Maybe the Moon by Armistead Maupin, printed, 1993 (Box 56)
  - Rat Bohemia by Sarah Schulman, printed, 1995 (Box 56)
  - A History of Gay Literature: The Male Tradition by Gregory Woods, printed, 1998 (Box 56)
  - Oriental Tales by Marguerite Yourcenar, printed, 1985 (Box 56)
  - Photographs, undated; 7 (Box 56)
  - Photographs, undated; 40 (Box 57)
  - Photographs, undated; 8 (Box 58)
  - Taxes, 1994-1996; 13 (Box 58)
  - Taxes, 1991-1995; 5 (Box 59)
  - Zeszyty 61 Literackie, 1998 (Box 59)
  - Vogue Deutsch, 1997 December (Box 59)
  - Out, 1997 September (Box 59)
  - Articles by and about Edmund White, 1994-1997; 18 (Box 59)
  - Articles by and about Edmund White, 1994-1997; 18 (Box 60)
  - "Rec'vd 1998 May", 1993-1998, undated; 3 (Box 60)
  - Postcards, undated; 4 (Box 60)
  - "Carrie D'Arts", undated; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973579)
  - "Dancing on a Tightrope", documentary reassessment of Jean Cocteau presented by Dr. Richard Mayne, undated; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973561)
  - Edmund White radio interview with Kay Bonetti, undated; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973553)
  - Elton, tape 1 (1 of 2 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973538)
  - Elton, tape 1 (2 of 2 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973546)
  - France Culture, undated; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973520)
  - Ed White interview with This Way Out, part I and II (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1977 September 22, 29; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973512)
  - Ed White interview with This Way Out, part III (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1997 October 6; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973504)
  - "What We've Done with You", Paris Cafes (and Ed's bit), undated; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002109973496)
  - The Book Show, Episode 199, 1997 October 6; YCALMSS808_0015; 1; 00:15:11 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002102339612)
  - The Book Show, Episode 200, 1997 May 8; YCALMSS808_0016; 1; 00:25:38 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002102339620)
  - "The Day the Shit Happened: A Melodocumentary Starring the Great Writer Edmund White," by Phil Cory 35 minutes, undated; YCALMSS808_0017; 1; 00:37:43 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002102339638)
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - "The Day the Shit Happened: A Melodocumentary Starring the Great Writer Edmund White," by Phil Cory 35 minutes, undated; YCALMSS808_0018; 1; 00:37:55; PAL (Box 61, Item barcode 39002102339646)
  - "Journal TV5", 1997; YCALMSS808_0019; 1; 00:29:20 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002102339653)
  - "Southbank Show- Genet", 1993 February 10; YCALMSS808_0020; 1; 00:55:06; PAL (Box 61, Item barcode 39002102339661)
- October 1998 Acquisition, 1995-1998; Series XVI; 1; (1 box)
  Purchased from Edmund White on the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 1998.
  Contains correspondence, writings, financial papers, photographs, audiocassettes, videocassettes and printed material by, to, or relating to Edmund White. Includes AIDS to Understanding, by Edmund White.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 577.
  - Articles by and about Edmund White, 1995-1998; 22 (Box 62)
- April 2001 Acquisition, 1947-1975; Series XVII; 1; (1 box)
  Purchased from Keith Fleming on the The Bradford F. and Lila L. Swan Fund, 2001.
  Contains correspondence between E. V. White and Delilah T. White concerning Edmund White, with related invoices and correspondence.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 124.
  - Psychoanalyst letters, 1957-1958 (Box 63)
  - Letters to Delilah T. White, 1947-1975, undated; 2 (Box 63)
  - Invoices, 1958 (Box 63)
  - College letters, 1958-1959 (Box 63)
  - Report cards, 1957-1959 (Box 63)
- November 2001 Acquisition, 1969-2001; Series XVIII; 8.71; (12 boxes)
  Purchased from Edmund White on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 2001.
  Boxes 53, 64, and 96 (CD, audiocassettes, and videocassettes): Restricted material required. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 73 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Contains correspondence, writings, printed material, audiovisual material, computer media, and other papers by or relating to Edmund White.
  Organized into four series: Miscellaneous Papers, Videocassettes, Audiocassettes, and Correspondence.
  - Miscellaneous papers
    - Unsorted correspondence, writings and printed material, [circa 1987-2001]; 12 (Box 64)
    - Photographs, undated; 7 (Box 64)
    - Slide, undated (Box 64)
    - Unidentified, undated; (1 audiocassette) (Box 64)
    - CD by rfi magazines "World Tracks, Voices, Rendezvous", 1998; (1 compact disk) (Box 64)
    - Unsorted correspondence, writings and printed material, [circa 1993-2000]; 6 (Box 64)
    - Unsorted correspondence, writings and printed material, [circa 1986-1993]; 25 (Box 65)
    - Journals, undated; 4 (Box 66)
    - Photographs, undated; 15 (Box 66)
      Includes correspondence.
    - Slides, undated (Box 66)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 66)
    - Letters from Edmund White to Drew Stund?, circa 1969 (Box 66)
    - Writings
      - "Shrinks", typescript, undated (Box 67)
      - "The Flaneur", proof, undated (Box 67)
      - "The Farewell Symphony", proof, undated; 2 (Box 67)
      - "The Married Man", proof, 2000; 3 (Box 67)
      - Notebooks, undated; 11 (Box 67)
      - Notebooks, 3 (Box 68)
      - La Revue, 1998 (Box 68)
      - Louis Stellner, Recent Work, 32 photographs; introduction by Edmund White, undated (Box 68)
      - Journals, undated; 5 (Box 68)
      - Our Paris, uncorrected proof, undated (Box 68)
      - "The Married Man", proofs, undated; 6 (Box 68)
      - "The Married Man", typescripts, undated; 6 (Box 69)
  - Videocassettes
    Box 96 (videocassettes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Charlie Rose: Camp David Summit with Edmund White", 2000 July 10; YCALMSS808_0010; 1; 00:57:18 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002102339562)
      Restricted fragile material.
    - "The Charlie Rose Show: Fonseca Panel", 2000 November 28; YCALMSS808_0011; 1; 00:16:05 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002102339570)
    - "Charlie Rose", undated; YCALMSS808_0012; 1; 00:57:46 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002102339588)
    - "The Lost Generation by Crisman Films, Inc.", 2001; YCALMSS808_0013; 1; 01:31:20 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002102339596)
    - "South Bank Show: White on WLT", 2001 September 7; YCALMSS808_0014; 1; 00:54:12 (Box 96, Item barcode 39002102339604)
  - Audiocassettes, 5
    Box 53 (audiocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Proust's Way, from BBC Radio 3, 2000 February 27; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973694)
    - Edmund White for my century, 1999 July 12; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973702)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973710)
    - Edmund White, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973728)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973736)
  - Correspondence, 14
    - Hubert Sorin's courtship letters to his wife Fabienne LeHooerou, undated; 2 (Box 70)
    - Incoming correspondence, 1999-2001; 12 (Box 70)
    - Unsorted correspondence, writings, and printed materials, 2000-2001; 4 (Box 70)
    - Unsorted correspondence, writings, and printed materials, 2000-2001; 3 (Box 71)
    - "A Mutual Sympathy": Metaphor in AIDS Literature by Sara Elizabeth Leary, 1999 (Box 71)
    - The Farewell Symphony, typescript, corrected, undated; 4 (Box 71)
    - The Farewell Symphony, photocopy, undated; 4 (Box 71)
  - Oversize
    - The Village Voice, 2001 (Box 72 (Oversize))
    - Posters for The Married Man and The Farewell Symphony, undated (Box 72 (Oversize))
  - Computer media
    - PARIS book: Ed White, 2001-ycal-0409-a-0001; 1 (Box 73)
- September 2003 Acquisition, Series XIX; 1; (1 box)
  Gift of Ecco Press, 2003.
  Contains proofs and typescript for Fanny: A Fiction.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 560.
  - Fanny: A Fiction, 1st pass- reader's set, 2003; 5 (Box 74)
  - Fanny: A Fiction, 3rd pass- reader's set, 2003; 5 (Box 74)
  - Fanny: A Fiction, typescript, 2003; 5 (Box 74)
  - Fanny: A Fiction, 1st pass- author's set, 2003; 6 (Box 74)
  - Fanny: A Fiction, 2nd pass- reader's set, 2003; 5 (Box 74)
  - Fanny: A Fiction, corrections, 2003 (Box 74)
- December 2004 Acquisition, 1999-2004; Series XX; 5.88; (8 boxes)
  Purchased from Edmund White on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 2004.
  Contains correspondence, writings, printed material, computer disks, audiocassettes, videocassettes, CDs and other related papers.
  Organized into three series: Correspondence, Writings and Related Papers, and Audiovisual Material.
  Boxes 80-81 (CDs, audiocassettes, and videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 82 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence
    - Bachardy, Don, 2004 (Box 75)
    - Banks, Melissa, 2001 November 5 (Box 75)
    - Gordon, Brad, 2002 (Box 75)
    - Gurganis, Allan, 1999 (Box 75)
    - Harrison, James, 2003 (Box 75)
    - Haslett, Adam, November 30 (Box 75)
    - Holleron, Andrew, 2002 Septemeber 7 (Box 75)
    - John, Augustus (son of), 2002 September 9 (Box 75)
    - Lipsyte, Sam, 2002-2003 (Box 75)
    - Lord, J., 2002 (Box 75)
    - Martines, Lauro, 2003 September 3 (Box 75)
    - Nabokov, Ivan, 2004, undated (Box 75)
    - Olds, Sharon, 2002-2003; 2 (Box 75)
    - Rushdie, Salman, undated (Box 75)
    - Trudy, 2003 October 6 (Box 75)
    - Vanderbilt, Gloria, 2004 (Box 75)
    - Wingfield, Garth, 2002 (Box 75)
    - Miscellaneous, 2002-2004; 3 (Box 75)
  - Writings and Related papers
    - My Lives, autograph manuscript, undated; 10 (Box 75)
    - My Lives, autograph manuscript, undated; 2 (Box 76)
    - My Lives, typescript drafts, undated; 12 (Box 76)
    - "Terre Haute", undated (Box 76)
    - Scorticatus Vivo, printed, 2001 (Box 76)
    - Unidentified notebook (Box 76)
    - Information relating to Proust, 2003 (Box 76)
    - Our Paris, proofs, 2001; 4 (Box 76)
    - Fanny: A Fiction, autograph manuscript, undated; 2 (Box 76)
    - Fanny: A Fiction, autograph manuscript, undated; 9 (Box 77)
    - Fanny: A Fiction, proofs, 2003; 21 (Box 77)
    - Fanny: A Fiction, drafts and editor's notes, undated; 4 (Box 77)
    - Fanny: A Fiction, drafts and editor's notes, undated; 15 (Box 78)
    - Fanny: A Fiction, research material, undated; 9 (Box 78)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 78)
    - Articles by or about White, 1999-2004, undated; 28 (Box 79)
  - Audiovisual Material
    Boxes 80-81 (CDs, digital audio tapes, audiocassettes, and videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - CDs
      - "A voix nue", undated; (5 compact discs) (Box 80)
      - "Cross-Cultural Poetics", undated; (1 compact disc) (Box 80)
      - "Richard Avedon: Portraits Antenna Audio Guide Metropolitan Museum of Art", 2002; (1 compact disc) (Box 80)
    - Digital Audio Tapes, undated
      - Sat Nite Out 14, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973835)
      - Gardens Trastevere interview, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973843)
      - Rome, Last Day, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973850)
      - (photos/song) Colosseum, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973876)
      - Letitia Clotti-Miller 8, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973884)
      - Ed, Rome, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973900)
      - Ed, Rome/Diana Arton, Trevi 1, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973868)
      - Trastevere 3, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973918)
      - Jeff Blynn, American, Rome 5, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973892)
    - Audiocassettes
      - Trollope on Trollope, BBC Radio 4, 2004 January 4; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973926)
      - Midmorning, MPR, undated; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973934)
      - Book Talk, 2002 January 19; 1 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002109973942)
        A handwritten note inserted in the case reads: Dear Edmund, Here's the program we've made from your Che[?] talk. Loved it - hope you're happy with this if yon [?] ! Best wishes, Jim
    - Videocassettes
      - TVO-imprint, L'Ecuyer interview with Edmund White, undated; YCALMSS808_0001; 1; 00:30:57; This was edited on 1997-09-22. (Box 81, Item barcode 39002102339471)
      - Third Annual Esther Freier Endowed Lecture in Literature, Edmund White, 2002 November 22; YCALMSS808_0002; 1; 01:17:13 (Box 81, Item barcode 39002102339489)
  - Computer media
    2004-ycal-1208-a-0001: My Lives
    2004-ycal-1208-a-0002: Scorticatus Vivo
    2004-ycal-1208-a-0003: Fanny: A Fiction
    2004-ycal-1208-a-0004: Articles by and about White
    - My Lives, undated
      - My Lives - final Before MC edit (Apple Works), 2004-ycal-1208-a-0001; 1 (Box 82)
      - MY LIVES (word) Patrick Merla version, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0002; 1 (Box 82)
      - MY LIVES (AppleWorks 5.0) Patrick Merla version, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0003; 1 (Box 82)
    - Scorticatus Vivo, undated
      - [no label information], 2004-ycal-1208-a-0004; 1 (Box 82)
    - Fanny: A Fiction, undated
      - FANNY WRIGHT - complete ms., 2004-ycal-1208-a-0009; 1 (Box 82)
    - Articles by and about White
      - all my articles, essays off both computers as of 6/22/02, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0010; 1 (Box 82)
      - McClatchy reviews Tchaikovsky, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0011; 1 (Box 82)
      - my articles (Mark Mitchell) Bunin [illegible], 2004-ycal-1208-a-0012; 1 (Box 82)
      - Herbert List, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0013; 1 (Box 82)
      - -Bisexuality (Garber) -Hamsun -YSL Ross Bluhner, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0014; 1 (Box 82)
      - Art + Life (Ann Arbor) Elton Oxford Genet + Homosexuality Jasper Johns Nabokov stories 1a photo, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0015; 1 (Box 82)
      - Proust speech on homosexuality, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0016; 1 (Box 82)
      - Robbe - Grillet in English, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0017; 1 (Box 82)
      - boyfriend - EW Wilde-, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0018; 1 (Box 82)
      - Colette Deneuve, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0019; 1 (Box 82)
      - Grace Paley, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0020; 1 (Box 82)
      - Clarendin, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0021; 1 (Box 82)
      - Alane in P[illegible], 2004-ycal-1208-a-0022; 1 (Box 82)
      - Flâneur Uncle Mame, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0023; 1 (Box 82)
      - Fanny Wright, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0024; 1 (Box 82)
      - Edmund White The Married Man (ClarisWorks 1.0), 2004-ycal-1208-a-0025; 1 (Box 82)
      - Edmund White The MARRIED MAN -- draft 2 (ClarisWorks 4.0), 2004-ycal-1208-a-0026; 1 (Box 82)
      - [no label information], 2004-ycal-1208-a-0027; 1 (Box 82)
      - DOMESTIC MANNERS OF THE AMERICANS EDMUND WHITE, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0028; 1 (Box 82)
    - Flaneur copies, undated
      - PARIS REVISIONS, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0005; 1 (Box 82)
      - PARIS ORIG. VERS. FLANEUR - FINAL, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0006; 1 (Box 82)
      - FLANEUR (final version), 2004-ycal-1208-a-0007; 1 (Box 82)
      - FLANEUR FINAL, 2004-ycal-1208-a-0008; 1 (Box 82)
- April 2005 Acquisition, 1972-2003; Series XXI; 5; (5 boxes)
  Gift of Edmund White, 2005.
  Contains contracts, financial papers and legal papers relating to Edmund White.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 778.
  - Married Man, undated (Box 83)
  - Married Foreign, 1996-2000; 2 (Box 83)
  - Married, undated; 4 (Box 83)
  - Proust, 1999-2002; 3 (Box 83)
  - Bloomsberg Paris, 1998-2001 (Box 83)
  - Fanny Wright (foreign), 1999-2000 (Box 83)
  - White Stories and miscellaneous, 1984-1994; 5 (Box 83)
  - White Miscellaneous, 1995; 6 (Box 83)
  - White Burning, 1992-1994 (Box 83)
  - Bergman, David, 1992-1993 (Box 83)
  - White Articles and Stories ECCU Press miscellaneous, 1992-2000 (Box 83)
  - White Caracole, 1985-1995 (Box 84)
  - The Darker Proof, 1987-1988 (Box 84)
  - The Farewell Symphony, 1997 (Box 84)
  - Genet, 1988-1995 (Box 84)
  - A Boy's Own Story, 1981-1998 (Box 84)
  - Beautiful Room, 1987-1993 (Box 84)
  - Nocturnes for the King of Naples, 1979-2001 (Box 84)
  - St. Martin's Nocturnes, 1998-1999 (Box 84)
  - Novel 6, 1996-1998 (Box 84)
  - Skinned Alive, 1993-1996 (Box 84)
  - White 1991 onward, 1991-2002 (Box 84)
  - White 1999, 1980-1990; 2 (Box 84)
  - Japan White, 1987-1998 (Box 84)
  - Japan Uni White - Burning Library, 1994-1999 (Box 84)
  - Japan White Caracole, 1993-1995 (Box 84)
  - Japan Uni White Skinned, 1996 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Essays, 1993-1998 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Gay Short, 1989-1992 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Nocturnes States, 1980-1996 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Darker Proof, 1987-1995 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White SS Skinned, 1993-1995 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Caracole, 1985-1987 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Sketches from memory, 1993-1994 (Box 84)
  - Nouvelle Agencie Rogers AWD, 1979-1994; 3 (Box 84)
  - States of Desire/Married, 1983-2000 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White ELENA, 1979-1984 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White BOYS, 1982-2000 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White ROOM, 1983-1990 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Genet, 1986-1997 (Box 84)
  - White Farewell, 1995-1998 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Farewell, 1997 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Married, 1997-2001 (Box 84)
  - RCW White Paris, 1998-2001 (Box 84)
  - Rogers White Misc, 1990-1996 (Box 84)
  - White/Proust, 1996-1998; 2 (Box 84)
  - White Married, 2000 (Box 84)
  - Brann-White Legal, 1995-1998 (Box 84)
  - Paris Review Elgrably Law Suit, 1995-1996 (Box 85)
  - Lapautre Genet, 1989-2002 (Box 85)
  - Bernabo, 1993-2002; 2 (Box 85)
  - Licht - Beautiful, 1988-1999 (Box 85)
  - Licht Genet, 1988-1993 (Box 85)
  - White Scandinavia, 1999 (Box 85)
  - Balcells Nocturnes, forgetting Elena, 1980-2002 (Box 85)
  - Balcells States of Desire, A Boy's Own Story, 1980-2001 (Box 85)
  - Balcells (Brazilian), 1994-2000 (Box 85)
  - All Foreign, 1993-2001; 2 (Box 85)
  - Kooy Genet, 1988-2001 (Box 85)
  - Mohrbooks Genet, 1987-2003 (Box 85)
  - Mohrbooks States of Desire, 1980-1988 (Box 85)
  - Mohrbooks A Boy's Own Story, 1982-1993 (Box 85)
  - Mohrbooks Nocturnes, 1979-1990 (Box 85)
  - Mohrbooks Beautiful Room, 1983-1988 (Box 85)
  - Mohrbooks Farewell, Skinned, 1994-2001 (Box 85)
  - Poland, 1996-1997 (Box 85)
  - Boy's Own Foreign, 1983-2001; 5 (Box 85)
  - Caracole, Dutton/Vintage, 1985-1995 (Box 85)
  - Caracole, foreign, 1985-2003 (Box 85)
  - Beautiful Room, 1982-1988; 2 (Box 85)
  - Boys, 1981-2001; 4 (Box 86)
  - Boys Own Story England and France, 1983-2000; 3 (Box 86)
  - Reverted Rights, 1980-2001; 2 (Box 86)
  - States: Foreign, 1980-2003; 2 (Box 86)
  - Forgetting Elena, 1972-1994 (Box 86)
  - Elena - Foreign, 1987-2000 (Box 86)
  - Nocturnes for the King of Naples, 1978-2001; 2 (Box 86)
  - The Beautiful Room is Empty (foreign), 1986-2002; 4 (Box 86)
  - The Darker Proof, 1987-2000 (Box 86)
  - The Darker Proof Foreign, 1987-2000; 2 (Box 86)
  - Faber - Faber Short Gay, 1989-2000; 2 (Box 87)
  - Genet: ECCO, 1987-1999 (Box 87)
  - Genet Foreign, 1988-2002; 3 (Box 87)
  - Albert Dichy, 1988-1996; 3 (Box 87)
  - Our Paris/Sketches from Memory, 1992-2003; 2 (Box 87)
  - Sketches for Memory, 1994-1999 (Box 87)
  - Knopf: Burning, Skinning, Farewell, 1993-1997 (Box 87)
  - British Contracts, 1989-2002; 2 (Box 87)
  - Skinned Alive foreign contracts, 1992-2003; 2 (Box 87)
  - Farewell Symphony foreign, 1999-2002; 2 (Box 87)
  - The Married Man Knopf, 1996-2002 (Box 87)
- December 2006 Acquisition, 1992-2006; Series XXII; 2; (2 boxes)
  Gift of and purchased from Edmund White on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2006.
  Contains writings, including drafts, correspondence, and printed material for Hotel de Dream and two autograph manuscript notebooks for My Lives.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 913.
  - The Married Man, French version, undated (Box 88)
  - Hotel de Dream, typescript, 2006; 2 (Box 88)
  - Hotel de Dream, notebooks, undated; 7 (Box 88)
  - Unidentified notebooks, undated; 3 (Box 88)
  - Paul Sorrentino notes, undated (Box 88)
  - Terre Haute, post presentation version, 2006 (Box 88)
  - Fanny: A Fiction, French version, 2004; 5 (Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 89)
  - Critique, 2001 (Box 89)
  - Fanny: A Fiction, promotional material, undated (Box 89)
  - Separate Rooms by Vittorio Tondelli, 1992 (Box 89)
  - Unsorted correspondence, 2002-2006 (Box 89)
  - My Lives, notebooks, undated (Box 89)
- November 2007 Acquisition, Series XXIII; 0.42; (1 box)
  Contains proofs for Hotel de Dream.
  Former call number: Uncat Mss 999.
  Gift of Harper Collins Publishers, 2007.
  - Hotel de Dream, setting manuscript, 2007 (Box 90)
  - Hotel de Dream, master, 2007 April 6 (Box 90)
  - Hotel de Dream, proof, 2007 May 31 (Box 90)
  - Hotel de Dream, AV's changes to first draft, 2007 April 6 (Box 90)
- January 2011 Acquisition, 2003-2010; Series XXIV; 1.21; (2 boxes)
  Contains writings, including an autograph manuscript for "Jack Holmes and His Friend," as well as correspondence and a photograph.
  Purchased from Edmund White on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2011.
  - "Jack Holmes and His Friend", manuscript, undated; 11 (Box 91)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 92)
  - Pages of "City Boy", undated (Box 92)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2010 (Box 92)
- November 2013 Acquisition, 2001-2013; Series XXV; 1; (1 box)
  Purchased from Edmund White on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2013.
  Contains correspondence, notebooks, drafts of writings (for "Paris in the Eighties" and "Paris Gossip"), and printed material.
  - Extra printed matter, 2001-2013, undated; 2 (Box 93)
  - Notebooks, undated; 2 (Box 93)
  - "Paris in the Eighties" and "Paris Gossip", manuscript, undated; 6 (Box 93)
  - Letters from writers, 2007-2013 (Box 93)
- Manuscript material removed from books, undated; 5 (Box 94)
- Newspaper clippings, 1997 (Box 95)